<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Material Me!</string>
    <string name="title_placeholder">Title</string>
    <string name="news_placeholder">News</string>
    <string name="sports_info_placeholder">Here is some news</string>

    <string-array name="sports_titles">
        <item>Baseball</item>
        <item>Badminton</item>
        <item>Basketball</item>
        <item>Bowling</item>
        <item>Cycling</item>
        <item>Golf</item>
        <item>Running</item>
        <item>Soccer</item>
        <item>Swimming</item>
        <item>Table Tennis</item>
        <item>Tennis</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="sports_info">
        <item>Here is some Baseball news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Badminton news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Basketball news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Bowling news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Cycling news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Golf news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Running news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Soccer news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Swimming news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Table Tennis news!</item>
        <item>Here is some Tennis news!</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sports_images">
        <item>@drawable/img_baseball</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_badminton</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_basketball</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_bowling</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_cycling</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_golf</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_running</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_soccer</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_swimming</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_tabletennis</item>
        <item>@drawable/img_tennis</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sports_details">
        <item>Baseball is a sport played between two teams usually of nine players each. It is a bat-and-ball game in which a pitcher throws ( pitches) a hard, fist-sized, leather-covered ball toward a batter on the opposing team.</item>
        <item>Badminton is a racquet sport played using racquets to hit a shuttlecock across a net. Although it may be played with larger teams, the most common forms of the game are "singles" (with one player per side) and "doubles" (with two players per side). Badminton is often played as a casual outdoor activity in a yard or on a beach; formal games are played on a rectangular indoor court. Points are scored by striking the shuttlecock with the racquet and landing it within the other team\'s half of the court.Each side may only strike the shuttlecock once before it passes over the net. Play ends once the shuttlecock has struck the floor or ground, or if a fault has been called by the umpire, service judge, or (in their absence) the opposing side.[1]</item>
        <item>Basketball is a team sport in which two teams, most commonly of five players each, opposing one another on a rectangular court, compete with the primary objective of shooting a basketball (approximately 9.4 inches (24 cm) in diameter) through the defender\'s hoop (a basket 18 inches (46 cm) in diameter mounted 10 feet (3.048 m) high to a backboard at each end of the court), while preventing the opposing team from shooting through their own hoop. A field goal is worth two points, unless made from behind the three-point line, when it is worth three. After a foul, timed play stops and the player fouled or designated to shoot a technical foul is given one, two or three one-point free throws. The team with the most points at the end of the game wins, but if regulation play expires with the score tied, an additional period of play (overtime) is mandated.</item>
        <item>Bowling is a target sport and recreational activity in which a player rolls a ball toward pins (in pin bowling) or another target (in target bowling). The term bowling usually refers to pin bowling (most commonly ten-pin bowling), though in the United Kingdom and Commonwealth countries, bowling could also refer to target bowling, such as lawn bowls.</item>
        <item>Cycling, also, when on a two-wheeled bicycle, called bicycling or biking, is the use of cycles for transport, recreation, exercise or sport.[1] People engaged in cycling are referred to as "cyclists",[2] "bicyclists",[3] or "bikers".[4] Apart from two-wheeled bicycles, "cycling" also includes the riding of unicycles, tricycles, quadricycles, recumbent and similar human-powered vehicles (HPVs).</item>
        <item>Golf is a club-and-ball sport in which players use various clubs to hit balls into a series of holes on a course in as few strokes as possible.Golf, unlike most ball games, cannot and does not use a standardized playing area, and coping with the varied terrains encountered on different courses is a key part of the game. Courses typically have either 18 or 9 holes, regions of terrain that each contain a cup, the hole that receives the ball. Each hole on a course contains a teeing ground to start from, and a putting green containing the cup. </item>
        <item>Running is a method of terrestrial locomotion allowing humans and other animals to move rapidly on foot. Running is a type of gait characterized by an aerial phase in which all feet are above the ground (though there are exceptions).[1] This is in contrast to walking, where one foot is always in contact with the ground, the legs are kept mostly straight and the center of gravity vaults over the stance leg or legs in an inverted pendulum fashion.</item>
        <item>The game of association football is played in accordance with the Laws of the Game, a set of rules that has been in effect since 1863 and maintained by the IFAB since 1886. The game is played with a football that is 68–70 cm (27–28 in) in circumference. The two teams compete to get the ball into the other teams goal (between the posts and under the bar), thereby scoring a goal. </item>
        <item>Swimming is the self-propulsion of a person through water, or other liquid, usually for recreation, sport, exercise, or survival. Locomotion is achieved through coordinated movement of the limbs and the body to achieve hydrodynamic thrust that results in directional motion. Humans can hold their breath underwater and undertake rudimentary locomotive swimming within weeks of birth, as a survival response.[1]</item>
        <item>Table tennis, also known as ping-pong and whiff-whaff, is a racket sport derived from tennis but distinguished by its playing surface being atop a stationary table, rather than the court on which players stand. Either individually or in teams of two, players take alternating turns returning a light, hollow ball over the tables net onto the opposing half of the court using small rackets until they fail to do so, which results in a point for the opponent.</item>
        <item>Tennis is a racket sport that is played either individually against a single opponent (singles) or between two teams of two players each (doubles). Each player uses a tennis racket that is strung with cord to strike a hollow rubber ball covered with felt over or around a net and into the opponents court. The object of the game is to manoeuvre the ball in such a way that the opponent is not able to play a valid return. The player who is unable to return the ball validly will not gain a point, while the opposite player will</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>